# Jeremy Chong

046 658 8421

jeremychong3000@gmail.com

Vermont South, VIC

A Surveyor with contemporary experience in techniques for gathering and presenting land measurements. Contributed to optimal land utilization as well as resolving land disputes by identifying legal boundaries and preparing plans and diagrams to present data to clients. Skilled in topographic, boundary, and feature survey types using high precision equipment such as total station and GNSS receivers as well as site analysis surveys done utilizing photogrammetry.

### **EXPERIENCE**

LAND SURVEYOR Vermont, VIC

Linear Land Surveying

July 2021 - Present

- Compiled measurement and marker data from Title plans and drawings using public records to determine geographical boundaries of land parcels and utility locations.
- Conduct Boundary reestablishment surveys along with topographical surveys.
- Consulted public records and contacted previous owners to conduct research on ownership, usage and zoning history.
- Assessed individual survey project needs and planned workflows.
- Performed field calculations to accurately show fencing boundaries in relation to titles.
- Set up precise measurement and control equipment as well as utilize GNSS equipment to connect to known benchmarks.
- Processing of field data to produce high quality plans representing existing features as well as fencing in relation to title.

SURVEY ASSISTANT Kensington, VIC

Headings & Associates

March 2021 - September 2021

- Produced detailed maps showing locations of boundaries and topographical features.
- Input and updated technical data for use in project reports and sketches.
- Utilized established field surveying strategies to perform high-quality work.
- Compared computations from field surveys against historical data and other documentation to determine accuracy of data
- Answered questions and provided information to public regarding assessment maps, surveys, boundaries and other concerns.
- Investigated land details such as deed information, zoning regulations and subdivision rules.

KITCHEN HAND Ringwood, VIC

The Coach

October 2020 - March 2021

- Maintained clean, trash-free workspaces to maximize productivity and safety.
- Inspected equipment, refrigerators and warming lamps to check compliance with safe operating levels.
- Followed proper handling and sanitation procedures to comply with food safety standards and protocols.
- Restocked supplies and prepared additional ingredients during downtime for expected busy periods.
- Made food according to standard recipes with requested changes for customer satisfaction.
- Compiled recipe ingredients and prepared for cooks by washing, cutting, or measuring food items.
- Cleaned and sanitized dishes and utensils, consistently keeping adequate supplies on hand for expected customer loads.

STAFF MEMBER Knoxfield, VIC

Hungry Jacks January 2016 - June 2020

- Established positive relationships with customers and other staff members.
- Responded sensitively and competently to service customers with diverse cultural backgrounds.
- Received and submitted cash, credit and check payments
- Kept work areas clean, organized and safe to promote efficiency and team safety.
- Greeted clients and guests and assisted with variety of questions to foster exceptional customer service.
- Maintained overall safe work environment with employee training programs and enforcement of safety procedures.

## **EDUCATION**

# **BACHELOR OF SCIENCE SURVEYING (HONOURS)**

RMIT University, Melbourne, VIC

Expected graduation Present

Dec 2018

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

Glen Waverly Secondary College, Glen Waverley

### ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Team Collaboration
- Verbal Communication
- Aerial Photogrammetry

- Critical Thinking
- GIS Knowledge
- Point Cloud Processing

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

• Certificate 3 in Hospitality

• Certificate 4 in Leadership & Management

#### REFERENCES

Samuel B — Linear Land Surveying Director (042) 294-6375 Sam@linearlandsurveying.com.au Christopher C — First Page Senior Web Developer (045) 038-5430 Chris.chong@firstpage.com.au